# Max Maievskyi

+49-1517-261-04-06 | MaksymMaievskyi@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/maksym-maievskyi | github.com/RedMaxMay

Current Location: Hamburg, Germany

## SUMMARY

As a passionate Front-End Developer with a solid foundation in relevant technologies, I'm confident in my ability to add value to any development team. I want to apply my skills and knowledge to a full-time role as a Front-End Developer, where I can further develop my expertise and contribute to creating outstanding digital solutions. In addition to my technical skills, my decade of experience leading teams has increased my soft skills quite well, so I think I can contribute to the success of your company.

#### EDUCATION

Tel-Ran.de GmbH React Frontend Developer

Company: Art Expert LLC

Kyiv National University of FT

Master's degree, Human Resources Management and Economics

Aug 2022 – Jun 2023 Berlin, Germany Sep 2008 - Aug 2013 Kyiv, Ukraine

Jan 2019 - Feb 2022

Kyiv, Ukraine

### Experience

#### Head of Department / Front-end Developer

• Continued as a department manager, leading a team of 12 people

Automated and optimized the department's work to achieve flawless results

• Learned HTML, CSS, and JS to create new e-commerce websites to grow the company

• Worked in a team to develop 2 e-commerce websites, a CRM, and a CMS:

\* Collaborated with the team to design UI/UX

\* Participated in the development of main pages, catalogs with sorting, shopping carts, and product pages and optimized everything for mobile devices (HTML, CSS, JS, Git, RestAPI).

**Head of Department** 

Nov 2014 - Jan 2019

Kyiv, Ukraine

Company: Art Expert LLC

- Expanded the company and created a new department
- Increased sales and profitability by over 200% in 3 years
- Managed a team of 10 people (set goals, monitored task completion, trained and analyzed department performance, etc.)
- Developed strategies to increase company profitability, optimized workflows, and proposed new ideas for growth

Designer-Manager Jul 2013 - Nov 2014 Kyiv, Ukraine

Company: Art Expert LLC

• Developed design solutions in Photoshop and Illustrator

- Expanded the company's client base through direct consultations and sales
- Contributed to the successful implementation of projects for restaurants and hotels
- Coordinated with the production department (created task lists and received completed work)

## My Portfolio and Pet projects

**PORTFOLIO** | All projects with links to live demo and code on github

maxmay-portfolio.netlify.app

Last projects (description):

"Green Shop" - E-commerce plants store | React, React Router, React Hooks, JavaScript, Semantic HTML5 markup, CSS custom properties, CSS Grid, Flexbox, Responsive Design, Axios, LocalStorage, CSS modules, REST API, Redux Toolkit

"Cars Info" - Explore the information about cars | Next JS 13, TypeScript, React, React Hooks, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, Responsive Design, Firebase API, Cars API

"MaxMay Media" - Online application for watching videos | React JS, React Hooks, JavaScript, Firebase API, Material UI, Material Icons, HTML5, CSS custom properties, Responsive Design, REST API

"Countries" - Get information about countries | Mobile-first workflow, React - JS library, Styled Components, HTML5, CSS custom properties, Responsive Design, Axios, REST API, React Router v6, React Icons

## Skills

Technical skills: React, Redux, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript, Responsive Design, Material UI, REST API, MySQL, Git, Photoshop, Illustrator, UX/UI design

Soft skills: My experience as a team manager has helped me develop strong skills in leadership, communication, and problem-solving.

Languages: English (B1-B2), Ukrainian (native), Russian (native)